Lucas William Bateson



Contact

Address:

Bekkelagsveien 20B Oslo, Norway 1177 Oslo

Phone:

+47 934 007 38

Email:

Lucas.bateson@gmail.com

Languages

English – Native Norwegian – Native German – Beginner (Studied for 3 years at school)

Summary

I am a 16-year-old student studying Information technology and Media production at Fyrstikkallen Vgs in Oslo, Norway. I am a British National, although I am born and raised in Oslo.

Skills

- Backend development using Python Flask.
- Vue.js frontend.

 Html, CSS and JavaScript for website creation.

Experience

Programming teacher Aug 2020 – Jun 2021

Oslo commune, Oslo

- Responsible for helping grade 4 students learn block programming.

Scout Leader Aug 2018 – present

Oslo

- Responsible for a patrol of 10 scouts ensuring well-being and safety on trips.
- Responsible for giving guidance to patrol leaders on how to lead their patrols.
- Gone through multiple courses with a focus on leadership skills

Media production Sept 2022 – present

Jordal AMFI, Oslo

- Doing replays for a live production of Ice hockey matches using a TriPlay.
- Doing camera work alongside a professional production team.

Education

Fyrstikkallen Vgs

Aug 2022 - Present

- Information technology and media production studies

Grades

Grades range from 1-6 with 1-2 being low competence, 3-4 being medium competence, and 5-6 being high competence:

- Programming 6
- Vocational Studies 6
- Maths 5
- English 5
- Science 5
- P.E 5
- Technological understanding 5
- Storytelling 5